A SHORT TIME AGO IN AN APARTMENT
IN PASADENA....
THE OPENING NIGHT EXCITATION
IT IS A PERIOD OF GREAT TENSION.
OUR HEROES, LEONARD, SHELDON,
WOLOWITZ AND KOOTHRAPPALI
KNOW THAT TICKETS
TO THE NEW STAR WARS MOVIE
ARE ABOUT TO BE AVAILABLE FOR PRE-SALE.
IF THEY FAIL IN THEIR MISSION
AND CAN'T SEE IT ON OPENING NIGHT
SHELDON HAS SWORN THAT
THEY WILL NEVER HEAR THE END OF IT
FOR THE REST OF THEIR LIVES...
THEY BELIEVE HIM.
-Guys, tickets already went on sale!
-What?
They're not supposed to be available yet.
I don't know what to tell you,
but they're on sale!
(STAMMERS) Wait. Are you sure
they're Star Wars tickets?
No, it's Steel Magnolias 2: Even Steelier.
The website's frozen. I can't get in!
-LEONARD: Yeah, me, too.
-Same here.
-Guys, they're gonna sell out!
-What are we gonna do?
All right, this goes
against everything I stand for,
but desperate times
call for desperate measures.
Lord...
This is Sheldon Cooper.
You're good friends with my mom.
I know I've spent my life
denying that you exist.
-Got 'em!
-Yeah, and I will continue to do so!
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
I'm really happy
you and Amy are back together.
PRESENT DAY
Thank you.
I'm also really happy,
but I can't pretend it's for you.
New Star Wars in three days! (CHUCKLES)
Hey, Thursday can't get here soon enough.
I'm taking off work
to watch the original trilogy
while I eat enough Star Wars
cereal to choke a Wookiee.
Uh, sweetie, you do realize
Thursday is Amy's birthday.
Yeah, and you do realize
I bought my ticket
when Amy and I were broken up?
I hope you didn't
need anything in that case,
'cause it's closed.
You guys just got back together.
You might not want
to ditch her on her birthday.
I think Penny has a point.
You can see it another day.
But someone might spoil the movie.
No, no one can spoil
Amy's birthday for me.
Surprise! She's even older.
Who saw that coming?
Aw! That's nice. Put that on her cake.
Oh, great. This again.
Arthur? What brings you back?
Beats me. I just
hope this isn't a sex dream.
In the past, you've come to me
when I'm struggling with a dilemma.
And... And the one time where...
Where you were afraid,
and you needed me for...
For a night light.
What's... What's troubling you?
Well...
My friends are telling me
I shouldn't abandon my girlfriend
on her birthday
to see the new Star Wars movie.
Well, sounds right.
Can... Can I get out of this mumu now?
Those are the robes of the Jedi,
the guardians of peace
and justice in the galaxy.
And they... They...
They don't wear underwear.
So, you agree with my friends
that I should skip the premiere?
Do... Do you love this girl?
Yes.
But she knows
how important Star Wars is to me.
Well, maybe you should show her how...
How important she is to you.
By seeing the movie she'd want me to see?
Sheldon, you can see this movie
whenever you want.
But you only have a limited number of days
that you can be with this woman.
Be with her.
You're right.
Great.
Where are you going?
I don't know,
but, hopefully,
somewhere I can wear pants.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Sheldon, what's wrong?
I wanted to let you know
I'll be spending your birthday with you.
Okay.
See, I had tickets
to the Star Wars premiere that night,
but Professor Proton
came to me in a dream,
dressed as Obi-Wan Kenobi,
and convinced me I should be with you.
Obi-what?
I'll let you get back to sleep now.
Good night.
Okay. Good night. Wait... Sheldon,
were you actually not gonna
spend my birthday with me?
(YAWNING) It's late. Got to go. Bye.
Good for Sheldon deciding
-to stay with Amy on her birthday.
-I know.
It's still gonna be weird
to see the movie without him.
Well, we could wait a couple of days
and see it together.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Hello.
Hey. We're going to the comic book store.
You want to come?
No, I can't.
I need to make preparations
for Amy's birthday.
Which leads me
to the following bit of business.
This is my ticket to Star Wars.
I don't have to tell you
it is worth far more
than its face value of $15.50.
I trust you'll give it to someone worthy.
You got it.
Well, Penny might want to join us--
This is my ticket to Star Wars.
-(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
-SHELDON: Penny? Penny? Penny?
What happens if I say, "Come in"?
Well, find out.
Come in!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
SHELDON: Bernadette?
Bernadette? Bernadette?
Come in!
Keep it up. I got nowhere else to be.
Just come in.
For future reference,
if I want to watch Mean Girls,
I'll stream it on Netflix.
We're sorry. What do you need?
Well, as you know,
I'll be celebrating
Amy's birthday with her,
and I could use your assistance
in helping me select the perfect gift.
-Sure.
-Well, so far,
I've come up with three ideas.
The first is a chance for her
to play the harp
with the LA Philharmonic.
Wow. You can really arrange that?
Well, I said a chance, you know.
When you tell them it's your birthday
at Bennigan's, they make a fuss.
I don't see why the Philharmonic
would be any different.
How about
something a little more realistic?
Well, Amy enjoys
knitting her own sweaters.
So, I was thinking
of getting her an all-expense-paid trip
to the Wisconsin Sheep & Wool Festival.
Sorry. I was waiting for the "bazinga."
Hold on. It could be romantic.
The two of them away together,
keeping each other warm
in snowy Wisconsin.
No, no, no, no. She'd be going alone.
But if you think I'm afraid of birds,
you should see me around sheep.
Okay, well, what's the third option?
That I have coitus with her.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
What do you think about
giving Sheldon's ticket to Stuart?
I don't know.
Have you ever
seen a movie with Stuart before?
It's like going with your grandpa.
Instead of eating popcorn,
he brings little pieces
of chicken in Tupperware
and a thermos full of soup.
He's not that bad.
Hey, Stuart, got any plans Thursday night?
My... My doctor's worried
about my circulation,
so I was thinking about
walking around the mall.
Why?
-Well--
-Hey, you guys.
Make sure to wear sensible shoes.
Wil, want to go to Star Wars, Thursday?
Absolutely.
Fine. Take Wil.
See if he brings you clam chowder.
Okay, okay, okay. Okay, okay...
Let's... Let's...
Let's just recap our options.
All right, we've got
harp thing, sheep thing...
Wild thang.
Which do you think she'd prefer?
Because I checked
the Sheep and Wool Festival website,
and there's only 8,000 tickets left.
Okay. Sheldon, being physical with Amy
is a huge step for you.
Yeah, are you ready for this?
Intimacy in any form
has been challenging for me,
but I'd like to show her
how important she is,
and it feels like
now might be the right time.
Sheldon, that's so beautiful.
Then it's settled.
Amy's birthday present
will be my genitals.
Thanks for taking me out.
Well, you're spending
your birthday with Sheldon.
Why not celebrate early?
So, where do you want to go?
I heard that new Mexican place
on Greene Street is good.
Sure, sure.
Or we could take you to get a bikini wax.
Why would I get a bikini wax
for my birthday?
(STAMMERS) I don't know.
It was just a thought.
I think I'll just stick to Mexican.
Great.
And then, maybe after,
we can watch a dirty movie,
and if anybody has any questions
about what happened or how,
we can answer them.
Okay, what is going on?
We just want you to be prepared
for any surprises
that might happen tomorrow.
What surprises?
(EXHALES)
We don't want to spoil anything,
but you should know that
Sheldon said he's ready to be physical.
You shut your damn mouth!
You actually heard him say this?
Yes. He said he wants to do something
to show you how much you mean to him.
(EXHALES)
I... I can't believe it. I...
I don't know what to say.
Well, we're really happy for you,
and we know how much he cares--
I do know what to say! Let's get me waxed!
Why isn't it ever
Angie Dickinson's bedroom?
You're back.
It... It doesn't seem like it's up to me.
I suppose you're here
because I've decided
to be physical with my girlfriend,
and I've never done that before.
Excuse me for a moment.
(LIGHTSABER ACTIVATING)
Well, it was worth a shot.
So, can you help me?
Uh, all right, um...
Once... Once the man gets
the woman out of her...
Out of her bloomers...
No. Not that.
I... I understand the mechanics.
Oh, good. Good. 'Cause
I have no idea what kids these days
are calling their... Their parts.
I think they say "junk."
What is happening to this world?
What... What do you
actually need to know?
This is an important night for us,
and I'm worried I might be overwhelmed
and ruin everything.
(SIGHS) Sheldon,
if you're with the right person,
it'll be okay.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Thank you, Arthur.
You are the wisest of the wise.
Well, that's...
That's very nice of you to say,
but I think I'm just an expression of...
Of your unconscious mind.
Oh, sure.
Well, you're fun to look at.
Tonight's the night!
Yeah, the wait is finally over!
I know.
Then you'll finally stop talking about it!
-Ready to go?
-Let's do this.
-Have fun, guys!
-We will.
-I can't believe Sheldon gave this up.
-I know.
We're gonna have
so much more fun than him.
No, they're not.
Knowing them, they will.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-T-minus 15 minutes!
-(ALL CHUCKLING)
-Oh, did you hear from Wil?
-Yeah, he's on his way.
Time for bladder check.
Check.
-Check.
Wait.
Screw it. I'm holding it.
(PEOPLE BOOING)
What is everyone booing at?
Hey, guys. What's up?
Uh... Hey, Wil. What you doin'?
I was on Star Trek.
Just rooting for the home team.
MAN: Star Trek stinks!
Yeah? Live long and suck it!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
SHELDON: Birthday girl?
Birthday girl? Birthday girl?
Come in!
Oh!
-Hi, Sheldon.
-Hello.
Sorry I'm late.
I also got you a balloon,
but it floated away,
and I chased it for a while.
That's okay. Come on in.
Thank you.
Um, I'll just... I'm gonna go
put these in water.
Okay.
Oh! This is different.
Hmm. Candles and music.
Do you like it?
It's kind of spooky.
I can change it back.
No, no, no. It's your birthday.
And as long as no one jumps out
in a hockey mask, I'll be fine.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
So...
What'd you have in mind for tonight?
I thought I could take you out
to a nice birthday dinner.
Now, if we pick a place east of here,
we might find the balloon.
Um, that sounds nice,
but I'm not really hungry right now.
I thought, maybe,
-we could do presents first.
-Oh!
All right. Um...
I should probably tell you
something about this gift.
You mean, before you...
Give it to me?
Yes.
May I ask you a question before I...
Give it to you?
-Of course.
-Why are we saying
"give it to you" like that?
Sheldon,
I know your present is
for us to be intimate tonight.
I see.
Is that all right?
I'm sorry,
but this is a litigious society.
I'm gonna need verbal consent.
Yes.
You know what, let me
pull a quick contract off the Internet--
So, if you don't like Star Wars,
why are you here?
Oh, I'm just having fun.
Everyone takes Star Wars so seriously.
Like if the movie's bad,
it's gonna ruin their lives.
Is it bad? Did you hear something?
Oh, my God. It's bad. Somebody kill me.
See? That's what I mean.
When you wake up in the morning,
whether this is the greatest movie ever
or a total piece of crap,
your life isn't gonna change at all.
He's right.
Yeah.
No matter what happens,
we're coming back tomorrow
to watch it again.
Do you think Sheldon's actually
gonna go through with it?
I don't know. He said he's ready.
Yeah, but he also swore this was the year
he'd be able to
pull the guts out of a pumpkin.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna stay positive.
I mean, we talked.
I told him what women like.
And after he stopped giggling,
he seemed pretty sure of himself.
(CHUCKLES) Hi.
Hello.
So, um...
Should I get under the covers with you?
All right.
-Hello--
-Hi!
Why are you shaking? Are you cold?
I'm just... (EXHALES) Really nervous.
Why?
Well,
I've been waiting for this for so long,
I've just built it up in my head.
I don't know what to expect.
Neither do I.
But, we can find out together.
Okay.
I'm really nervous.
I know.
We've been waiting so long for this.
And we've built it up
in our heads so much.
Guys, it's just a movie.
-That's true.
-He's right.
-It is.
-(CHUCKLES)
Although, we all remember Jar Jar.
Leonard, I'm scared again.
A FEW HOURS LATER,
IN A BEDROOM NOT FAR AWAY....
Well, I enjoyed that
more than I thought I would.
Me, too.
I look forward to your next
birthday when we do it again.
That works for me!
I enjoyed that
more than I thought I would.
I don't think I can walk right now.
ARTHUR: Sheldon?
Sheldon.
Arthur.
What are you doing here?
I... I... I don't think
I need any more advice.
I... I was just curious.
How did it go?
It was amazing.
I... I saw it a few days later.
What a movie.
But, what... What about Amy?
Oh! Uh...
She liked it fine.
Yeah, but she doesn't have the history
with the franchise I do.
Okay.
Good... Good talk.